Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep
within your dreams Taking aim
for your heart so it would
seem Stand tall and read,
go to hell and jump for
paradise Every time dangerous,
dangerous We like it serious, serious,
oh Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today
Adventure calls now,
let's go The balls filled between us, they
will show Still what we don't know Yes,
working hard together Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
Despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through We're living in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers
All the love and the tears
In the world we're in
United gently bringing up Our thought
again, yeah We're the foolish ones we love,
we'll carry on
Till we see the light, the sun will rise
The greatest fight at its core is
against myself forevermore Come on,
let's do it now,
let's go The balls filled between us,
they will show So what we don't know,
that's what we call adventure Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers
Superpowers
Yes, we've got superpowers
Superpowers Yes, we've got superpowers
Superpowers Yes, we're the superpowers!
Superpowers!
Yes, we're the superpowers!
Candy! Candy!
Slug-e-e!
What are you talking about, Nami?
What's happening over there?
Hey, come on!
If that hits us, we're all dead.
We can go to burst, can't we?
No!
We're short on Call!
Poor Pedro!
He sacrificed himself to save us enough!
Everyone, listen.
I'm ready for my kids now!
Little lickety-minutes, please! Stop!
You can't do this, Mama!
Sink the ship, and you'll
sink the cake along with it!
Are you listening?
Quickly! Yes, sir!
How's this?
Seem about right, Jinbei?
Yes!
That's good enough!
This is madness!
You're steering the ship and
moving the sails by hand?
Nami! The wind?
There's a strong gust
coming from the south!
All right!
What's the plan?
I'm lost!
I'm tacky!
Straight into the wind!
If you turn, we'll crush
it in the wave, won't we?
Not if we can get inside the green room.
Let's go.
No!
Wait, what's the green room?
I'm scared!
Why are we going into the lake, Stephen?
Oh, I see!
The green room is like a
metaphor for heaven, right?
Doctor!
I might be seeing you
sooner than I thought!
It's over!
You can't just surf your
way out of this mess!
Oh, I'm sorry, Pedro!
All right, hang on, here we go!
What's wrong, are you guys okay?
Hey!
Can you hear me?
Someone, say something!
Zoe, in heaven, it's beautiful.
This is a damn fine ship!
The green room is a brief wave room
that forms inside a collapsing wave.
I used to play in these often as a boy.
They're quite popular
with young fishermen.
What?
So this is...
We're inside the wave!
Hold on tight!
We're sailing through!
You have a fine vessel
and a fine navigator.
With a strong helmsman.
This ship is invincible.
Unreal.
It's so agile and fast.
Like this ship's part of his own body.
I've never seen a helmsman.
Steal like this.
You're cool, Jinbei.
So we're not gonna die!
Where is my cake?
Dammit!
Not ideal, but fine.
They got what they deserved,
the little scoundrels.
My little lie about the wedding
cake was swallowed by the sea.
Hello, Otakuri.
Better's better here.
We took care of them.
They're all dead.
Hey! Brooke! Nami!
Answer me! Chopper! Koby!
Oopsie-daisy.
Well, shoot.
Guess we're not invading after all.
The plan's a wash, you guys.
The ship sank.
Looks like you'll just have
to burn down something else.
What? Yeah?
I'm not so sure.
The other side of the mirror doesn't
look like it's underwater to me.
You see?
What's going on here?
Well, fine. Ha!
We've still got this.
Shoot one more round just to be safe.
What happened?
The mirror broke all of a sudden!
Why does this have to be so complicated?
Why did you break the mirror?
Luffy needs that to come back
to the Sunny, doesn't he?
It'll take all I've got to
beat the guy I'm fighting.
We have to break every mirror on the ship.
Otherwise, Luffy will get
hurt trying to protect us.
Yeah, but...
Look, we can't get in his way.
It's the captain's orders now, go!
They still have some mirrors left.
I see one, Joska—we all see it, Mascar.
Ready
to start some fires anytime, anyplace!
If it looks like a mirror,
then smash it. Understand me?
me
Now, fire!
He-he-he!
Ah!
What? What?
Why did the mirror break?
Alright, only one more!
You don't think they're alive, do you?
Pedos said they sank and he
wouldn't have a reason to lie to us.
The mirror's probably shattered
because of the water pressure then.
Makes sense.
Oh, you're right, that does make sense.
Something's not right here.
Hey, hey, Puffy!
You okay? Chopper!
Shh!
We need to talk, so get
away from the enemies!
So you guys are okay after all?
Hey!
Straw Hats, run and stop him!
What's going on over there?
That candy guy told people to Sonny sink!
It was gonna sink until
Kaido bailed us out!
I wish he could've seen it!
We'd be at the bottom of the sea!
Anyway, we're fine, so don't worry.
And also, we broke all the
mirrors on the ship like you said.
Good work!
Thanks, you guys!
It's nice that the enemies can't come
to the ship, but now neither can you!
Yeah, but don't worry.
I'll figure it out.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
You don't even have a plan!
Fortunately for you, I do.
Sanji is baking a cake on
Kaku Island. He'll be okay.
We're headed there right now.
But it's gonna be at least
10 hours before we make it.
So around 1 a .m.
First things first, kick that guy's ass.
Then look for a mirror
that leads to Kaku Island.
And we'll meet you there, okay?
I'm stuck!
Damn it!
What just happened?
Did you hear the plan?
Luffy!
You got this right!
Come on!
That can't be a good sign, can it?
Still there, Luffy?
Hello?
Tell us you're okay!
Say something!
Willow Mochi
Max. Max.
Max.
Oh, no!
Get to that island as fast as you can!
I'll wrap this up in no time, so
you better not keep me waiting!
Okay!
Alright, see you soon! Yeah!
The enemy will probably start coming
after us again, so keep watch!
Roger that.
Let's go to the observation deck, Carrot.
Okie Dock, Chobro!
My friends are waiting, you'll say.
I'm not gonna die here.
You realize those may be your last words.
My friends are waiting.
I'm not going to die here.
It's only natural for you to
rage against your own demise.
But all the same, this will be your end.
you could fight but if you just keeled
over right now that would be nice
a tree stop calling me a tree and
don't act like your Candy attitude will
get you through this my brother's more
than strong he's undefeated unbeatable
a warrior of superhuman talent who's
never fallen on his back a single day
In fact, the moment he was born, he
stood on his feet and slept on a chair.
So the legend says, he's never lain
down and never been knocked down either.
Why, he's downright
disrespectful to the ground.
His bearing is always noble,
cool-headed and strong.
There's not a single flaw about him.
That's our big brother.
He's the shining star
of the Charlotte family,
whereas you're nothing
but a wee little brat.
Ha, you should apologize with your life!
Shut up, tree, just go away!
You keep your hands off my little sister.
Katakuri!
Watching thrust!
That was close!
Stabbing me wasn't enough.
The name of this trident
is mole by the way.
Should I start with a hand or a foot,
which would you like to lose first?
I'll sever it for you.
Start with a stupid head, please?
Could you shut the hell up!
Now gomp gomp!
Giant rifle!
I was listening.
Straw Hat.
I heard what you said.
I know where you've been attempting
to meet up with your crew.
Wanna play with the big wave again, Mama?
Come on, I promise it'll be fun!
Are you even listening?
What?
The ship hasn't sunk yet, you say?
And what makes you think that?
I heard them talking, I'm sure of it.
You didn't see the size of
the candy monster's wave!
It swallowed that ship whole!
Escape was not lickety-likely.
How they did it doesn't really matter.
The point is, I'm certain
they're still alive.
And they will be showing up at
Cacao Island after midnight.
That's exactly what they
promised to that Straw Hat.
There's no question.
But they have no clue that I know that.
So let's prepare a welcoming
party for them, shall we?
Hey, Mama.
Turns out that cake you want is
in Chocolatown on Cacao Island.
Let's head there now.
I lickety-like to her out of desperation.
But if this plays out, it'll be like
I was telling the truth all along.
Pudding is baking the cake
at Cacao Island, after all.
This could still go south, but it looks
like the pieces are falling into place.
Oh, wedding cat!
Over there?
You got it!
Stop! No! No!
That's Nuts Island!
Are you guys even lickety-listening to me?
That's not where the
wedding cake is going, Mama.
We need to head to Cacao
Island or you won't get it.
Wedding cake!
Yes, yes, but not there.
Stop, I'm going to lickety-lose my mind.
He never learns.
How about this? Help!
Now, Gum-Gum!
Aaaaaaahhh!
Uh!
Ah!
Damn it!
He knows exactly where I'm going
to dodge every single time!
Swearing me out!
The feeling is mutual.
No one's ever evaded so many
of my attacks for so long.
It's stressful.
Were you trying to grab my mole?
Yeah, I'll get it next time for sure.
Flowing mochi.
Whoa, what?
We're turned into mochi!
This is just like what Doe Flamingo did!
Listen closely, rookie.
My Devil Fruit's power ascended.
They've reached a new horizon.
A higher state known as awakening.
It's only natural that
my ability has awakened.
It's no use.
And there's no pot of tea to
help you escape this time.
I could just chop you up.
Or I could let the mochi
suffocate you on its own.
How would you like to die?
I am not gonna die!
Fourth gear.
This just got interesting.
Something isn't right.
Feels like we should have gotten the
location of Straw Hat's ship by now.
Does this mean something
happened to the territory slugs?
Peckhams, that's enough out of you!
Stop your crying already!
But I'm sad about Pedro!
I'm sympathetic.
Pedro was like a brother to Peckham,
so having him meet such an end,
c 'est une tragedy terrible.
What, are you friends?
Well...
I can't die just yet.
The dawn of the new world is coming soon.
I can't rest until I've seen it!
This should be more than enough
to undo all of your little tricks.
That's dynamite!
Adios.
Friend of all, this came
to me as a bit of a shock.
I saw Pedro five years ago.
Fighting part of this part.
To hold on to every moment of his life.
That my mom might spare.
It's that same man was willing.
To sacrifice his life and on his tongue.
To help the Straw Hats.
You getting at something here?
Perhaps we're making an error.
After all, there are many who have paid
the price for underestimating Straw Hat.
What are you proposing?
Simply that we should be
more cautious on this matter.
Mama won't lose to some brat.
You're implying that Straw Hat is
so weak that it's part dangerous?
Compared to Mama?
Straw Hat is nothing but a joke.
Now, you would still say that
looking at the state of the Shit?
Clearly that was an accident!
And the territory slugs!
Is it an accident as well that
they're failing to function right now?
What?
You think they planned all of this?
That we're playing into some trap?
I'll put it this way.
En Serious, unexpected incidents has
been occurring ever since they got here.
A champion's pride comes before a fall.
Is it not our job to protect
Mama's honor? Therefore,
in order to prevent further accidents,
let us dispatch a fleet to protect
the borders of our territory.
Excuse me, Mondore? What?
The Lady Custard would
like to speak with you.
Custard was chasing
after Veggie, wasn't she?
Yes, this is Mondore.
You would better have
some good news for me.
Wow!
The thing is, we lost
Veggie's ship. You won!
For some reason, the territory slugs
aren't sending us its location. Great.
It's not just us. What?
We were trying to drag Straw Hat's ship,
and the damn territory slugs
weren't giving us a thing!
Are you serious?
Just go and look for
Veggie on your own. Do not.
And I repeat, do not
let him escape. Got it.
Click.
Hey, go check on them right away. On who?
What the hell do you
think I'm talking about
on the territory slugs screwing us over?
Yes, sir. Damn it.
I'll get to the bottom of this.
Didn't think they'd give
up the chase quite so easy.
Wonder what the deal is.
Maybe the territory slugs don't know
where we're trying to go, little old.
Are they jammed or what? Dunno.
But if they were operating like usual,
then our transponder
snails would be reacting,
wouldn't they?
Maybe they're sleeping
on the job, little old.
You think so?
I've never heard of that happening before.
I'm not complaining, though.
Let's keep hauling ass, boys.
My lady is waiting for me.
Head this ship straight to Cacao
Island to be quick about it!
This is Nasorta calling from Jerma's ship.
How'd the battle go?
Good news?
We marched in with 10,000
soldiers and crushed them.
Their kingdom is devastated.
That's my brother.
You had me worried.
Are you kidding?
Jerma's nothing.
With our strength, it was easy.
Quick question, though.
You didn't destroy the manufacturing
system for the clones, did you?
Course not. Don't you worry.
I know that was our objective.
But other than that, the place is wrecked.
As it should be, brother.
Those chair-ma-grunts were doomed
the moment we had them in our sights.
What's going on with
Strawhead and his friends?
It's a mess.
They made it out to sea.
They're trying to escape to the west.
Well, it's no matter.
We'll catch them soon enough.
I'll leave that in your capable hands.
Thanks, and nice work.
Click.
Wow, that was pretty easy.
Well, that's good news.
Luffy is safe.
What's next?
There's nothing tying us down.
Set sail.
You know where.
Roger that.
Muscle balloon!
I tire of watching this
meaningless future play out.
Why should I allow you to power up?
Listen up, Straw Hat!
From now on, I won't underestimate you.
Mirror Moshi!
The ceiling spoke to you too?
Crap, if that comes down on me,
I'm going to be buried alive!
Yes, you'll suffocate.
Finally, it ends.
Sorry to kill you in such an undignified
manner, but I was getting a bit impatient,
you see.
Since you gave me so much trouble, I'm
40 minutes late for today's merienda,
my afternoon snack.
Your suffering will end soon.
This is goodbye, Straw Hat.